stampd.com 2019-03-18

# Privacy Policy – Stampd

What do we do with your information?

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

## CONSENT

How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.

If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

How do I withdraw my consent?

If after you optin, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting us at info@stampdla.com or mailing us at:  
Cornerman Productions, LLC DBA  
Stampd  
1368 Elwood St  
Los Angeles, California 90021

## DISCLOSURE

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

### Payment:

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then our server stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCIDSS).

Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCIDSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.

PCIDSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

## THIRD PARTY SERVICES

In general, the third party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store's website or are redirected to a third party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website's Terms of Service.

### Links

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

## SECURITY

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCIDSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

## COOKIES

How do we use cookies?

To store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc). Visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider's internal stats tracker to record the number of visits Unique, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.

Cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart. _secure_session_id, unique token, sessional storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

## AGE OF CONSENT

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

### LEGAL NOTICE

All content on this site, including, but not limited to: informational content, graphic images, and program code such as html and JavaScript are the copy written material of Cornerman Productions LLC. and may not be reproduced in any manner without the expressed written consent of Cornerman Productions LLC.

All prices listed are accurate to the best of our ability. In the rare case an item is mis-listed, Cornerman Productions LLC reserves the right to refuse to sell the item at the listed price.

Please note that upon placing an order, a receipt is automatically mailed confirming the purchase intent. This receipt does not constitute a contract, and orders may be canceled at any time due to insufficient stock, inability to authorize a credit card, suspicion of fraudulent intent, discovery of an incorrect item price, or any other reason, as we see fit. Please further note that Cornerman Productions LLC. shall have the right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not your credit card has been charged. If your credit card has already been charged and your order is canceled, Cornerman Productions LLC. shall issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the incorrect price.

## QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at info@stampdla.com.
